alticeusa.com 2017-06-22

# Privacy Notice | Altice

**Website Privacy Notice**

Neptune Holding US Corp. ("Altice") owns and operates this website. In this Privacy Notice, "we," "us," "Altice," and "our" refer to Neptune Holding US Corp. and its affiliates. We use the term "visitor" to refer to any person or entity who accesses any part of the website for any amount of time through any means.

**To our website visitors**  \- Altice respects your privacy rights. This Website Privacy Notice ("Privacy Notice") is designed to provide you with information about how Altice protects your privacy in connection with your use of this website. By accessing or using this website, you accept this Privacy Notice.

**To our subscribers**  \- This Privacy Notice does not govern Altice’s treatment of information it collects and receives about you in connection with products and/or services provided to you by Altice. Instead, it governs the information it may collect and/or receive through this website. Altice's services are governed by separate privacy notices and agreements.

**A. How we collect visitor information**  
We may collect, maintain, and access certain information you provide and information collected from your use of the website and services available through the website. This visitor information may include information that can be associated with you personally ("Personally Identifiable Information"). Visitor information may include, among other things, your first and last name, your home addresses, and your telephone number. 

We will collect Personally Identifiable Information about you when you voluntarily provide it to us. When you use website features that ask you for certain information, you provide Personally Identifiable Information. You can navigate through the website without giving us Personally Identifiable Information, but certain activities are only available to our subscribers who provide us such information.

Personally Identifiable Information does not include aggregated data, anonymized information, or other information that does not identify a particular person. We may generate anonymized or aggregated information from the information we collect. This is information from which any Personally Identifiable Information has been removed. Anonymized or aggregated information does not identify you. Our collection, use, and disclosure of anonymized and aggregated information are not subject to any of the restrictions in this Privacy Notice. Anonymized or aggregated information may include, among other things, Internet server and browser identification, the Internet service provider, duration of visit, and domain type. This aggregated information will not reveal any Personally Identifiable Information about any specific visitor.

We may also collect visitor information in the following ways:

  * **Cookies.**  Similar to most website operators, we use "cookies" to collect information about your visit to our website and to manage information concerning your preferences. A cookie is a small encrypted computer code added to a file on your computer as a record of your visit. It does not collect or provide your name or any other personal information about you. It can, however, be used by this website to note information about your visit, such as your type of web browser, operating system and Internet Protocol address, to better tailor the site for you. It can also be used to recognize you when you return as a repeat visitor to our website. We use cookies, for example, to monitor the times when visitors log-on to the website, to track the number of sweepstakes and promotions you enter, to estimate the audience size of the website for sponsors and advertisers, and to track visitor preferences. Cookies do not allow the website to access Personally Identifiable Information that you have not otherwise provided. You can control what cookies are accepted by your computer through the settings on your web browser or by deleting them from your computer. Doing so, however, may limit the personalization available to you. We, our third party service providers, advertisers or our partners also may use cookies to help deliver, manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Altice network of sites or other networks or sites, or to send you customized ads about our own products and services as you access other websites and web services. This may also help us, our service providers and partners provide more relevant advertising. For more information regarding third-party ad servers, see "Service providers' and other third parties' collection and use of information" below.
  * Clear GIFs. Like many websites, we may use clear GIFs (also known as "web beacons," "Internet tags," or "pixel tags"). Clear GIFs are lines of code that allow websites to summarize overall visitor usage patterns and to provide personalized services. We may use clear GIFs, for instance, to track visitor preferences or to gather aggregated information about visitor usage patterns. We do not use clear GIFs to collect any Personally Identifiable Information about visitors.
  * Passive Automatic Electronic Collection. Like operators of most other websites, we collect and log information automatically, either directly or through a third party service provider. For example, we collect your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, the name and location of your Internet Service Provider, the type and version of your browser, the length of time you visit the website, your search queries on the website, and the average number of pages you viewed. Logging your IP address does not by itself provide us with your name, e-mail address, or home or work address. We use this log information for systems administration purposes and for technical troubleshooting. We may also use it to gather general demographic information about you, such as your general location.

**B. How we use visitor information**

We use Personally Identifiable Information collected from visitors for several important purposes, including:

  * to protect the security of visitors and the website;
  * to help prevent fraud; and
  * to provide you with a website and services of enhanced value to you.

We also use anonymized or aggregated information to improve website services, to gauge the effectiveness of the website, and to improve and enhance visitors' experiences on the website.

**C. When we disclose visitor information**

Except as described in this Privacy Notice, we will not disclose Personally Identifiable Information collected through the website to entities other than to Altice affiliates unless (a) it is necessary to enable us to provide services or to conduct legitimate business activities related to the website; or (b) you give your consent before we disclose your Personally Identifiable Information.

We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with persons or companies who help us operate the website by providing maintenance and technical services. We may also provide your Personally Identifiable Information to other third parties when you expressly consent.

We contractually require our service providers to maintain at least the same level of confidentiality for the Personally Identifiable Information we provide to them as we maintain for such information. Additionally, we require that our service providers' use of such information not exceed that needed to provide the service.

You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if we are required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary (a) to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process; (b) to investigate violations of this Privacy Notice, our Terms of Use, or other contracts we have with you; (c) to respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) to respond to your requests; and (e) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the public, Altice, its agents, its users, or the website.

We reserve the right to disclose and transfer your visitor information, including your Personally Identifiable Information, in the event of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all, or components, of our business.

**D. How long we will keep visitor information**

Altice may retain Personally Identifiable Information and other information collected through the website for as long as is reasonable for the purposes for which it was collected.

**E. How we protect visitor information**

We follow industry-standard practices to protect information collected through the website. Visitors' Personally Identifiable Information is stored in Altice databases in physically secure facilities. If we share visitor information with Altice affiliates, the affiliate will follow similar practices to protect Personally Identifiable Information collected through the website.

Any information transmitted over the Internet may be subject to breaches of security. Although we follow commercially reasonable practices to securely store the information we collect and to work with responsible third parties, we cannot guarantee these practices will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use, or disclose such information.

**F. Third party collection and use of information**

This website may include links to websites of Altice affiliates and non-Altice entities. These affiliates and other entities may solicit and collect Personally Identifiable Information and may store cookies on website visitors' computers. When you leave this website to visit the website of an Altice affiliate or of another entity, you will be subject to the privacy Notice and terms of use agreement of that website operator. Altice is not responsible for the ads, links, content, activities, or information practices of other websites.

**G. How we protect children's online privacy**

This website is not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have received Personally Identifiable Information of a child under 13, we will delete the information from our records.

**H. Notice to visitors from outside the U.S.**

The website is published in the United States. By visiting this website, by using services offered through the website, or by providing Personally Identifiable Information to us or to our service providers, you agree that we may collect, use, and disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as described in this Privacy Notice, including by transferring such information from the country where you live to the United States.

**I. Notice to California residents: Your California Privacy Rights**

Individuals who reside in California and who have provided their Personally Identifiable Information to the website may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following address:

Neptune Holding US Corp.  
Attn. Shared Services Dept  
6 Corporate Center Drive  
Melville NY 11747

Such requests may be made only once each calendar year. We may not respond to requests sent to addresses other than the one shown above.

**J. Changes to this Privacy Notice**

We may change this Privacy Notice at any time. We will notify you of material changes by posting the revised Privacy Notice on the website. We encourage you to periodically review the Website Privacy Notice to inform yourself of any changes. The revised Privacy Notice will be effective on the date it is posted unless the revised notice states otherwise. If you use the website after the effective date of the revised Privacy Notice, we will conclude that you accept the revised Privacy Notice.

**K. Questions about this Notice**

Please contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Notice:

Neptune Holding US Corp.  
Attn. Shared Services Dept  
6 Corporate Center Drive  
Melville NY 11747

**Effective June 21, 2016**
